

# Sviatoslav Tyshchyk

## Front-end developer

## **About Me**

I have been working as a developer for MetaTrader for the last 3 years on a freelance basis, Upwork mainly. I developed various trading robots/scripts that simplify trading. Developing was performed using MQL language, it's very similar to C++.. Also, I have experience in QA, I worked for Gameloft company in 2019 in Lviv's office.

## **Professional Experience**

QA tester at Gameloft 2019-2019

Team of 14 people Project: Asphalt 9

#### Responsibilities:

- Collaboration with developers and team
- Analyze Specifications
- Execute Tests
- Document Bugs
- Troubleshoot Issues

#### MQL developer/Freelancer Upwork 2019 – present

#### Responsibilities:

- Gather info from clients regarding products.
- Negotiated and consult technical aspects
- Create a documentation
- · Developing and maintenance
- Make sure that client's expectations are met

Tools & Technologies: MQ4, MQ5, Telegram API, C++, SQLite, Pine Script

## Languages

- Ukrainian: native
- English: Upper intermediate

## **My Contact**

- svet.tyshchyk@gmail.com
- Thttps://github.com/STyshchyk
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/svyurie/
- nttps://www.instagram.com/sv.yurie/
- **(** +380682372585

## **Education**

Ukrainian National Forestry University

Bachelor in Forestry Engineering 2013-2017

Project and achievements

- 3D scanning in Forestry
- Second place in annual University conference
- Ukrainian National Forestry University

Master in Forestry Engineering 2013-2019

Project and achievements

- Second place in annual University conference
- Graduated from the university with honors
- Front-end at https://rs.school/
- Institute Of Leadership, Management And Coaching

**Soft Skill** 

Negotiation

Adaptability

Problem-solving

Time management

2022 - Present Professional coach

### **Hard Skill**

- CSS3/HTML5
- SCSS
- Webpack
- JavaScript
- Git
- Bootstrap
- React
- Material UI
- Rest API
- SQL